Our story began one fateful day...
I wasn't pretending to sleep
in the warm, spring sun.
This is just how I spend my breaks in peace,
as a guy with no friends in his class.
That's all for our stream today.
Sorry guys.
- See you in the next one.
- Bye for now.
- And done.
- Cool.
- How about a post-stream selfie?
- Sure.
Wanna join in, Asamiya?
No thanks.
- Sure. You ready?
- Always.
Dude, I'm not in the shot.
Fix your aim.
It's been one month since the semester began.
Which means it's time to change seats.
- Seriously?
- Score!
Seats will be chosen at random.
Come draw your lot.
And don't dawdle.
Next.
- I'm over there!
- Screw you, man.
I got a great spot.
Man, I hate being up front.
Yeah, I'll be right in the teacher's vision.
Let's swap.
- You need the front seat.
- My eyesight's not that bad.
This is fine.
I like my ordinary, uneventful life.
Everyone situated?
Then pass your worksheets up front.
Settle down already.
Huh?
I thought I was just fine with the ordinary.
But this one seat change
flipped my mundane high school life
right upside down.
[I like you.]
[Adapted from Mashiroito's work of the same title]
I'll take this one.
Today's the day I get one.
Because if I don't...
Easy now.
[Principal's Original Bread! Just 120 Yen]
Here you are.
Thanks, ma'am.
I'll take this one.
That'll be 180 yen.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Are you sold out today?
- Yes, so sorry.
- Aw man...
He's gonna blow his fuse again...
Here.
Have this last one.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Thanks!
- I'll take this.
- That'll be 180 yen.
Mayama.
I've still got plenty right here.
Then I'll take one.
That'll be 120 yen.
Right.
Here you are.
Thanks for purchasing.
I'll always have some in stock.
What was with that note this morning?
[I like you.]
Is he pranking me?
No one would fall for this.
We're an all-boys school.
Could I get your worksheets?
Asamiya, um...
Your note here.
Window row, you almost done?
If you're going to erase it,
why write anything at all?
Hold on.
What if that note wasn't a prank?
No way...
Was Asamiya confessing to someone in our row?
No, impossible.
I'm jumping to wild conclusions.
Ms. Komori?
No, that can't be it.
Right?
I don't know.
Maybe he likes older women.
Wait, does that mean I got in his way?
This is bad.
This is really, really bad.
Because Asamiya, he's...
He's got the brains and the looks.
He's the highest tier guy in our school.
If I actually did piss him off,
my high school career is over.
His smile, it's too bright...
What are you doing?
Huh?
It's the real deal.
Nothing.
What? What now?
Mind if I join you?
Huh?
What exactly is going on here?
What's that?
Bread.
Made by the principal.
People actually eat his stuff?
The good bread was sold out.
He's mad... right?
I mean, I think he is.
Asamiya.
That note...
Sorry, I know you weren't expecting it.
You could say that.
But I meant every word.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't realize you were serious.
And here I am, getting in your way...
Huh?
I made you erase your note for Ms. Komori.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
I know apologizing doesn't help, but...
No, that's not...
I'm so, so sorry.
That note was for you.
Right, thought so.
Wait, what?
It was for you.
For me?
Are you pulling my leg?
- No.
- Oh, okay.
So, the note.
Why me?
Because I like you, why else?
Right.
That doesn't answer anything.
This is the first time we've spoken, though.
It's not.
It's not?
I figured you wouldn't remember.
Well, I mean...
What about me do you even...
Asamiya, what's keeping you?
Sorry, be right there.
Mayama.
If you want to know why I like you...
Well, you'll find out.
[Mayama]
I'm so confused.
Why...
Because I like you, why else?
Mayama.
If you want to know why I like you...
Well, you'll find out.
Why me?
- Morning.
- Hey.
Eat quick, or you'll be late.
Mom and Dad already left for work.
You have more trophies.
Huh? Oh.
Anyway, I have to get to work.
I'd understand if he were into my brother…
What was that?
Nothing.
See you later.
Morning.
Morning?
Why are you here?
I was waiting for you.
Hurry, we'll be late.
Huh?
Sorry.
Mayama?
I'm fine.
Everyone got their papers?
What the heck am I doing?
I didn't have to run.
Like me or not,
anyone would be offended by my attitude.
I've got to apologize.
Ready? Begin.
Hey, can I borrow an eraser?
Sure.
Pencils down.
Pass your tests up front.
[Your bed hair, your hunched back]
[You never prioritize yourself]
Right. Of course.
Nothing.
[Your bed hair, your hunched back]
[You never prioritize yourself]
I've got the bread.
There he is!
- Finally!
- Thanks, man.
You're so useful to have around.
Seriously.
I want a croqutte bread.
Could I have one, too?
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
Thanks.
These are all negative traits of mine.
I knew it. Asamiya was just pulling my leg.
Sorry.
Do you have a minute?
Sit.
Sure.
So, what'd you need?
I wanted to clear up the misunderstanding.
Huh?
My sticky notes.
No, you made yourself loud and clear.
If anything, you're helping.
Keep pointing out my bad traits.
I'm sure there's more you've picked up on.
Maybe lots more, actually.
I knew there was a misunderstanding.
Huh?
I wasn't pointing out anything bad.
These are stuff I like about you.
What?
I told you that you'd find out, right?
I like your bedhead.
I like how you hunch over.
And...
You prioritize others,
even at your own expense.
Because you're kind.
Mayama?
No one's ever said that about me before.
Hold on.
Here.
I managed to beat the crowd and get one.
Here, it's all yours.
Thanks.
- How much was it?
- It's fine.
I wanted to buy one.
But I'm the one eating it.
Then how about this.
Can I make a request?
A request?
I want to touch your bed hair.
- What?
- You can say no.
I mean, it's fine.
It just doesn't exactly feel fair?
An opportunity to touch you
is plenty fulfilling for me.
If you insist.
Go ahead.
- Pause.
- What?
If you go slow, it's ticklish.
Relax.
Should I stop?
It's fine.
Sorry I offended you this morning.
This morning?
You waited for me, and I pushed you away.
I wasn't offended.
You weren't?
No. I was too busy admiring you.
I thought I made you hate me.
That'd never happen.
I would never come to hate you.
So, Asamiya.
When you said you "liked" me...
Never mind.
What?
You got some on your cheek.
You like me...
as a friend, right?
Right?
Cheers to us.
You kept your bed hair intact.
[Preview]
Mayama, you've become best buds with Asamiya.
Smells like Asamiya.
Something good happen?
Huh?
You said you liked me, but...
You meant as friends, right?
- What do you think?
- What do you think of Asamiya?
I don't know. I guess he feels far away?
If Asamiya feels so far, then get close!
You only "like" me
as a friend, right?
Of course not.